Richard York Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artists' Artwork Files, circa 1865-2004, Series 2:; (Boxes 7-64; 56.85 linear feet)
  - General, circa 1865-2004, 2.1:
    - Laessle, Albert, 4791CY: Chanticleer, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - La Farge, John, 3066CY: Yellow Roses, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - La Farge, John, 5056JY: Near Green River, Wyoming, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - La Farge, John, 8943RY: Sun Coming Over Mountain, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 1293CY: Roses in Oriental Vase, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 1412JY (7542CY): Pink and Yellow Roses, 1984-1985, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 1629CY: Still Life, 1985-1988 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 2702RY: Roses on a Wall, 1989-2000 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 3810RY: Wisteria on a Wall, 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 4235CY: Roses in an Oriental Vase, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 7542RY: Roses on a Wall, 1981, 1990, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 8783CY: Roses, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran, 9097CY: Wisteria, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Lane, Fitz Hugh, 3429CY: Star Light in Harbor, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Lane, Fitz Hugh, 3629CY: The Clipper Ship "Spitfire" Under Full Sail, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Lane, Fitz Hugh, 4625RY: Sunset at Gloucester Harbor, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Lane, Fitz Hugh, 6006RY: View of West Beach, Beverly, Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Lane, Fitz Hugh, 7759CY: Mount Desert Rocks, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - [Placeholder], 2002, September 5 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Lanman, Charles, 743CY: Riverside Stroll, Adirondacks, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Lanman, Charles, 8969CY: Landscape, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Lathrop, William L., 651CY: Little Will's Lime Kiln, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Lathrop, William L., 3026CY: Red Shale Road, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Laurent, Robert, 2560RY: Plant Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Laurent, Robert, 2561RY: Acrobat, 1988-1995 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Laurent, Robert, 2741RY: The Bathers, 1989-1990, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Laurent, Robert, 4570CY: Rooster, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Laurent, Robert, 5088CY: Dog, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Laux, August, 4005CY: Pomegranates, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Lawrence, Jacob, 2716JY: The Plowman, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1006RY: Connecticut Landscape, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1125CY: Brooklyn Bridge, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1374CY: Miami Beach, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1375CY: New England Landscape, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1440CY: Cheyennes Mountains, Colorado, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1441CY: The Valley, 1984-circa 1985 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1877CY: Lyric, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 1998CY: The Valley, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 2032CY: The Mill, 1987, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 3085CY: River Landscape in Winter, 1990-1992 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Lawson, Ernest, 4619CY: Harbor Scene, 1995-2001 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 681RY: Tulips, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 682RY: Flowers, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 908CY: Abstraction, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 909CY: Abstraction II, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1041CY: Provincetown Houses, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1149CY: Abstraction, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1154CY: Dunes Over October, 1982-1988 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1178CY: Provincetown Backyards, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1179CY: Abstraction #1, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1180CY: Abstraction in Black and White, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1388CY: Provincetown Backyards, 1984-1988 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1761CY: Red Carnations, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1762CY: The Anchor, 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1776CY: Provincetown Dunes, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 2570RY: Woodstock, New York, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 2610LY: Abstraction in Green and Gold, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 3118CY: Provincetown Houses, 1990-1992 (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 3209CYabc: My Wharf Studio, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 3210CY: Beach Combings, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 3335CY: Calendula, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 82)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 3719CY: Red Skow, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 4600LY: Provincetown Houses, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 4748CY: Provincetown Houses, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - Learned, Henry, 5098LY: Near Eudora, Kansas, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Leavitt, Edward Chalmers, 1703RY: Still Life with Cherries and Oranges, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 87)
    - Leavitt, Edward Chalmers, 3461CY: Pears, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - Lee, Doris, 1484CY: Sketches, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - Lee, Joseph, 4995CY: Ralston Hall and Its Grounds, San Mateo County, California, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - Le Grand, Henry, 1672CY: Boys Fishing, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - Leigh, William R., 4441CY: Indian Pony with White Man's Saddle, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - Lembeck, Jack, 4150RY: Trigger's Jigger, 1994-1997 (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - Lemmen, Georges, (1844CY): Seated Woman, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - Lepper, Robert, 1908RY: Coal Loader, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - Lepper, Robert, 1909RY: Three Machine Age Paintings, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - Lepper, Robert, 1910RY: The Piston, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 97)
    - Leutze, Emmanuel, 2857CY: The Crusaders' Return, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 98)
    - Lever, Hayley, 1403CY: Two Mast Schooner, Eastern Point, Gloucester, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 99)
    - Lever, Hayley, 1901CY: Broadway at 95th Street, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 100)
    - Lever, Hayley, 2107CY: Coming Storm, Cornwall, England, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 101)
    - Lever, Hayley, 2670CY: Broadway at 95th Street, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 102)
    - Lever, Hayley, 6131CY: Spring Flowers in my Garden, Caldwell, New Jersey, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 103)
    - Levy, Alexander Oscar, 1287JY: The Ostrich Fan, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Lewandowski, Edmund, 3060CY: Dynamo, 1990-1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Lewandowski, Edmund, 3161CY: Steel Structures, 1991-1994 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lewandowski, Edmund, 4485CY: Railroad Diesels, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Lewandowski, Edmund, 4780CY: Amish Farmscape, No. 4, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Lewandowski, Edmund, 5026CY: Lifeboat, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Lewin, James Morgan, 2763RY: Peaches, Grapes and Berries, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Lewis, Edmund Darch, 4081CY: A View Near the New Jersey Coast, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Leyendecker, Joseph C., 4445CY: Saturday Evening Post Cover, Jan. 1909, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Libbey, Walter, 7130CY: Double Self-Portrait, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 4102CY: Her Hero, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Lie, Jonas, 4636CY: Harbor Scene, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Lieberman, Max, 2209CY: School Girl Running, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 3028CY: Story in Paint, 1990-1992 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4461CY: Camellias, March 1933, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4462CY: Cannes - 1930, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4463CY: In a Southern Hotel, St. Augustine, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4464CY: Bedroom Interior, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4465CY: Red Camellia, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4466CY: Silver Wedding, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4467CY: Synthesis - In the Swiss Mountains, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 4583CY: Landscape, circa 1995 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Liebman, Aline M., 6613CY: Camellias for Christmas, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8586RY: Filipendula Ulmaria; English Meadow-Sweet, Queen of the Meadow (II, pt. III, 53), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8610RY: Rubus Idaeus, var. Aculeatissimus; Fruit of Wild Red Raspberry (II, pt. III, 77), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8617RY: Rhododendron Miximum; Great Laurel, Rose Bay (II, pt. IV, 84), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8619RY: Kalmia Latifolia; Mountain Laurel, Spoon-Wood, Calico Bush (II, pt. IV, 86), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8623RY: Andromeda Glaucophylla; Wild Rosemary, Moorwort (II, pt. IV, 90), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8624RY: Vaccinum Corymbosum; Swamp or High-Bush Blueberry, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8627RY: Clethra Alinfolia; Sweet Pepperbush, White Alder (II, pt. IV, 94), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8628RY: Pyrola Americana; Shin-Leaf, Wintergreen (II, pt. IV, 95), 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8632RY: Monotropa Uniflora; Indian Pipe, Corpse Plant (II, pt. IV, 99), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8638RY: Cypripedium Parviflorum, var. Pubescens; Larger Yellow Lady's Slipper (IV, pt. VII, 155), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8639RY: Cypripedium Acaule; Moccasin Flower, Stemless Lady's Slipper (IV, pt. VII, 156), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8672RY: Prunella Vulgaris; Self-Heal, Heal-All (IV, pt. VIII, 189), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8674RY: Veronica Virginica; Culver's Root, Culver's Physic (IV, pt. VIII, 191), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8676RY: Verbascum Blattaria; Moth Mullen (IV, pt. VIII, 193), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8683RY: Gerardia Virginicia; Smooth Falso Foxglove (IV, pt. VIII, 200), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8684RY: Trillium Undulation; Painted Trillium, Birthroot, Wake Robin (III, pt. V, 101), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8685RY: Trillium Grandiflorum; White Trillium (III, pt. V, 102), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8694RY: Polygonatum Biflorum; Small Solomon's Seal (III, pt. V, 111), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8701RY: Clintonia Borealis; Fruit of Yellow Clintonia (III, pt. V, 118), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8706RY: Viola Cuculata; Early Blue Violet (III, pt. V, 123), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8707RY: Convolvulus Sepium; Hedge Bindweed, Morning Glory (III, pt. V, 124), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8710RY: Typa Latifolia; Broad-Leaved Flag, Cat-Tail Flag (III, pt. VI, 127), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8716RY: Castalia Odorata; Sweet-Scented Water Lily, Pond Lily, Water Nymph (III, pt. VI, 133), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8717RY: Nymphaea Adrena; Yellow Pond Lily, Spatter-Dock, Cow Lily (III, pt. VI, 134), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8721RY: Agrostemma Githago; Corn Cockle, Corn Rose, Corn Campion (III, pt. VI, 138), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8728RY: Anemone Cylindria and Anemone Virgiana; Long-Fruited Anemone and Tall Anemone, Thimbleweed (III, pt. VI, 145), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8731RY: Clematis Virginiana; Fruit of Clematis (III, pt. VI, 148), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8732RY: Aquilegia Canadensis; Wild Columbine, Honeysuckle (III, pt. VI, 149), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8736RY: Betula Lutea; Yellow or Gray Birch (SS, pt. XIII, 303), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8739RY: Anemonella Thalictroides; Rue Anemone (SS, pt. XIII, 306), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8756RY: Acer Spicatum; Mountain Maple (SS, pt. XIII, 323), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8758RY: Ceratium Arvense; Mouse-Ear Chickweed (SS, pt. XIII, 325), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8762RY: Trillium Cernuum; Nodding Trillium (SS, pt. XIV, 329), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8775RY: Conopholis Americana; Squaw-Root, Cancer Root (SS, pt. XIV, 343), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Lincoln, Edwin Hale, 8778RY: Cornus Circinata; Round-Leaved Dogwood or Cornel (SS, pt. XIV, 346), 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Lincoln Handkerchief, 2786CY, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Lindberg, Arthur Harold, 2175RY: Archer-Daniels-Midland Co. Elevator - South, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Lindberg, Arthur Harold, 9399CY: Donner-Hanna Coke Co., 2003 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Linton, William James, 1379RY: Still Life with Grapes, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Lloyd, George, 9416CY-9419CY, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Lloyd, George, 9416CY: Wrecked Auto, 2003-2004 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Lloyd, George, 9417CY: Endymion, 2003-[2004] (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Lloyd, George, 9418CY: The Anchorite, 2003-[2004] (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Lloyd, George, 9419CY: L'Acquaiola, 2003-[2004] (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Locke, Charles, 1974CY: Remnants, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Loew, Michael, 8962CY: Fourth of July, 2002, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Loomis, Chester, 4304CY: Beach at St. Vaast, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Low, Mary Louise Fairchild MacMonnies, 2015RY: The Kitten, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 306CY: Bridge Repairs, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 460CY: Minneapolis, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 810CY: Bird of Paradise, circa 1981 (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 2135CY: Omaha, 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 2136CY: Wash Day, 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 2137CY: Lumberjack, 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3114CY: New York, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3121CY: Bird of Paradise, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 79)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3133CY: Tanks #2 (Steel Plant), 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 80)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3143CY: Minneapolis, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 81)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3135CY: High Bridge, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 82)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3136CY: Corner of Steel Plant, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 83)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3137CY: High Bridge (II), 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 84)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3138CY: Backyards of Broadway, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 85)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3139CY: Tanks #1, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 86)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3140CY: Brooklyn Bridge, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 87)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3141CY: Into the Canyon, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 88)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3142CY: Bridge in Shadow, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 89)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3143CY: Third Avenue (Third Avenue El), 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 90)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3144CY: Coney Island (Luna Park), 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 91)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3145CY: Luna Park, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 92)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3146CY: Moscow, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 93)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3147CY: What Never Happened, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 94)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3148CY: Snow Plow in New York, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 95)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3149CY: Sledding in New Jersey, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 96)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3150CY: Sick Tree, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 97)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3151CY: Barge Canal, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 98)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3152CY: River, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 99)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3153CY: Lone Worshiper, 1990-1997 (Box 33, Folder 100)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3154CY: Still Life #2 (With Apples), 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 101)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3164CY: Allen Street (Under the Elm), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 102)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3165CY: Hanover Square, 1991, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 103)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3166CY: High Voltage - COS COB, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 104)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3167CY: Through Brooklyn Bridge Cables, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 105)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3168CY: Blast Furnaces, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 106)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3169CY: Breakfast (Still Life, Breakfast), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 107)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3170CY: Coal Pockets #1, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 108)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3171CY: Construction (Excavation), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 109)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3172CY: Self-Portrait (Portrait Study), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 110)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3173CY: Traffic, 1991, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 111)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3174CY: Under the Bridge, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 112)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3175CY: White Tanks, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 113)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3176CY: Elevated Railway, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 114)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3177CY: Mid-Air, 1991, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 115)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3178CY: First Avenue Market, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 116)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3179CY: In a Quarry, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 117)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3180CY: Granite for Monuments, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 118)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3181CY: Emergency Job, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 119)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3182CY: Granaries of Democracy, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 120)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3183CY (A-L): A Tribute to American Industry (Calendar), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 121)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3243CY: Construction #2, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 122)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3244CY: Loading (Loading Girders), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 123)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3245CY: Sentinel, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 124)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3246CY: Above the City, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 125)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3247CY: Storm Clouds Above Manhattan [After the Storm (Clouds Over Manhattan); Clouds Above Manhattan; Storm Over Manhattan], 1991 (Box 33, Folder 126)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3248CY: In a Quarry (In the Quarries; Granite #2), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 127)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3249CY: Steel Valley, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 128)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3250CY: Open Mine (Crushed Rock), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 129)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3251CY: Slum Clearance (Demolition), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 130)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3252CY: After the Fire (Snow After a Fire), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 131)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3253CY: Winter Fun, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 132)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3254CY: Granite (Granite #1), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 133)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 3362CY: Queensboro Bridge, 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 134)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 4488CY: Coney Island (Luna Park), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 135)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 4530CY: Brooklyn Bridge, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 136)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 4531CY: Coney Island (Luna Park), 1991, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 137)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 4722CY: Williamsburg Bridge, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 138)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 2170RY: Still Life: Dahlias and Apples, 1987-2003 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 2348RY: The Red Barn, 1988-1999 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 2727CY: Sea Abstract, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3110RY: Bread and Fruit, 1987-1988, 1997-2003 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3186CY: Pear, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3192CY: Variations in Blue, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3196CY: Arrangement in Space, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3197CY: White and Gold, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3198CY: Arrangement in Blue and White, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3199CY: Through the Bottle, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3200CY: A Remembrance, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3201LY: Variations in Green and White, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3204CY: In View of Lake Champlain, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3215CY: The Yellow Tablecloth, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3216CY: Design for Rhythm, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3217CY: Close Harmony, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3218LY: Toccata in Green, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3219LY: Sea Abstract, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3220CY: Still Life: Eggplant and Jawbone, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3221LY: Blue and White, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3222LY: Fruit and Flowers, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3223LY: Still Life with Potted Plant, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3224LY: Purple Flask and Lemon, 1991, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3232CY: Classic Head, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3233CY: Day Lily in Pewter, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3238CY: Still Life with Yellow Cloth, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3240CY: Red and Variations, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3241LY: Still Life with Phone, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3242LY: Still Life with Irises and Tulips, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3255CY: Birches, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3256CY: Bust of a Young Man, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3257CY: Single Flower, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3258CY: Lily of the Valley, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3259CY: Standing Nude Woman from Behind, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3260CY: Standing Male Nude, Arms at Side, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3261CY: Standing Nude Woman/Interlaced Fingers, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3262CY: Reclining Male Nude, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3263CY: Standing Female Nude/Arms Raised, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3264CY: Back of Standing Nude Man, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3265CY: Still Life: Indian Motif, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3288CY: Church in Italy, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3305RY: Bread and Fruit with Checkered Cloth, 1991, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3307LY: Stairway, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3308LY: Flower in Vase, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3309LY: Fountain, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3310LY: Fountain, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3311LY: Rowboat, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3312LY: Building, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3313LY: Pine Tree and Tiger Lilies, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3314LY: Building, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3315LY: Fruit Tree, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3316LY: Waterscape, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3317LY: Building, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3318LY: Gone West, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3319LY: Landscape, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3320LY: Standing Nude, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3321LY: Skyline, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, 3322LY: Landscape, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 58)